funtoosh.com 2013-06-06

# Privacy Statement - Funtoosh.com

## Privacy Statement for Funtoosh.com - The Humor portal 

**Funtoosh.com - The Humor portal** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ Funtoosh.com - The Humor portal ](http://www.funtoosh.com/)

Funtoosh.com regards all information collected from its online members as completely confidential. This includes email address provided during the Newsletter registration processes. Funtoosh.com will never let out your email-address, to any external parties or any other web sites.

#### Cookies 

Our Site uses cookies  for delivering content but we do not track any personal user information via these cookies or share this info with any third-parties. Please do note that we serve ads on our site from third party advertisers and these advertisers might place cookies or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process, we do no store or have no access to this info. 

#### Forums & Subscription lists

We use public forums on the site (http://forums.funtoosh.com) Your Email address and any other data you provide us will never be released to a third party. All our Email lists use the Opt-In model. These Emails always include a procedure and instructions to remove yourself from our lists. 

Certain sections (forums) of this site log and display your IP address. We use this procedure for your protection as well as our own. It helps us protect our members from abuse. 

#### Advertisers 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies, cookies received with these ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

We also use Google Ads on our site, and these ads might place a [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) please do note that the following info regarding the cookie placed via ads served via google. * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.  
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

#### Personal Information 

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. 

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. If in the future If we do collect personal information It will be kept completely confidential. 

#### External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **Funtoosh.com - The Humor portal** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

## Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us via this [form.](http://www.funtoosh.com/comments_sugg.htm)
